https://entrinsik.com/informer/entrinsik-privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy  Entrinsik Privacy Policy
FeaturesSolutionsGovernmentEducationAgency InsuranceMortgageTitle InsuranceManufacturingDistributionInformer for MultiValueResourcesCustomer StoriesWhite PapersWebinarsVideo SeriesPartnersRequest a demoSupportHelp Informer 4Training/ConsultingHelp Informer 5Referral Program FeaturesSolutionsGovernmentEducationAgency InsuranceMortgageTitle InsuranceManufacturingDistributionInformer for MultiValueResourcesCustomer StoriesWhite PapersWebinarsVideo SeriesPartnersRequest a demoSupportHelp Informer 4Training/ConsultingHelp Informer 5Referral Program PRODUCT TOUR
Entrinsik Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy relates exclusively to information supplied by you on this website.ENTRINSIK respects the privacy of your personal information. Any personal information provided by you to ENTRINSIK through this Website will be used solely to deliver to you with the information and services you have requested at this Website, to update and enhance ENTRINSIK records, and to advise you of other products and services that may be of interest to you. This policy will not alter or affect any information otherwise provided by you to ENTRINSIK.The details that you are requested to provide on this Website may be transferred within ENTRINSIK which may include transfer to other parts of the company in different jurisdictions, and by using this Website you consent to such transfer. In providing your email address, telephone number, mailing address, and fax number you are agreeing that ENTRINSIK may contact you by email, telephone, mail, and fax.Your details may be disclosed by ENTRINSIK to its authorized resellers for purposes of contacting you to provide sales and support service. Otherwise, your details will not be revealed by ENTRINSIK to any unaffiliated third parties, unless ENTRINSIK has your permission or is under either a legal obligation or any other duty to do so. The information provided by you on this Website may be disclosed by ENTRINSIK to regulators, lawyers, auditors, third-party service providers, and any agent acting on our behalf.The information collected from you by ENTRINSIK will be valuable in improving the design and marketing of our range of services and related products for customer use. ENTRINSIK wishes to assure you that your private information will be treated as confidential and with high standards of security. The use of your information will be kept to the minimum required for ENTRINSIK to continually monitor and improve its services to our customers and to keep you informed about our products, services, and other opportunities within ENTRINSIK. ENTRINSIK pledges its intention to comply with the requirements of data protection/privacy laws in the jurisdictions where ENTRINSIK offices are located. Data provided by you is retained as long as the purpose for which the data was collected continues; the data is then destroyed unless its retention is required to satisfy legal, regulatory, or accounting requirements or to protect ENTRINSIK interests.ENTRINSIK reserves the right to amend its privacy policy at any time and will place any such amendments on this Website. All revised terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on this site. If ENTRINSIK makes any significant changes, we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on our Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. This Privacy Policy is not intended to, nor does it, create any contractual rights whatsoever or any other legal rights, nor does it create any obligations on ENTRINSIK with respect to any other party or on behalf of any party.Entrinsik is a global business. We may transfer personal information to countries other than the country in which the data was originally collected. These countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your personal information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.Cookies and Similar Technologies By visiting our Website cookies will be placed on your device (computer, mobile or tablet). A “cookie” is a small text file that is placed on your device by websites you visit. Some of the cookies we use are strictly necessary to operate our Website . Others relate to the Website ‘s performance and functionality and to your preferences. ENTRINSIK uses the following cookies and similar technologies on the Website :1. Strictly necessary: These cookies enable the Website to function correctly and deliver the services and products you have requested. These cookies do not gather information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering sites you have visited on the internet.2. Performance & functionality: These cookies do things like remember your preferred language, understand your preferences and associates users to any forms you submit to use to enable pre-completion of subsequent forms. Other cookies are placed only for the time or session you visit our Website or whether you are a new or returning visitor to our Website.3. Analytics: We use a third-party analytics tool to help us analyze how our Website is used, such as allowing us to compile reports on website activity and providing us other services relating to website activity and internet usage. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website may be transmitted to and stored on a server located outside the country where you live.4. Third-Party Remarketing Cookies: These are cookies used by third-party companies that we trust to show you ad banners on other websites.You can generally opt out of the use of cookies by changing your browser settings. For more information about cookies, visit http://www.aboutcookies.org. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the Website site, you will be able to view our sites, however, you will not experience a personalized visit.If you have questions regarding any of your personal data held by us, please contact us at sales@entrinsik.com.
